Finding Aid for Ann Arbor Woman’s Club (Mich.) records, 1906-1983
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Ann Arbor Woman’s Club (Mich.) records 1906-1983
Ann Arbor Woman’s Club (Mich.).
3 linear feet
85666 Bk.w 2
Minutes of meetings, annual reports, secretary and treasurer's books, scrapbooks, and miscellaneous clippings, budgets and newsletters.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were deposited by the organization (donor no. 1312 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The Ann Arbor Woman's Club was established in 1906.
The records of the Ann Arbor Woman's Club have been arranged into the following series: Secretary's records; Annual and other reports; Miscellanea; Treasurer's record books; Scrapbooks; and Photographs.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.); Women--Michigan--Ann Arbor--Societies and clubs.
Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
- Secretary's records
  - Secretary's book, 1906-1908 (Box 1)
  - Minutes
    - 1910-1923, 13 folders (Box 1)
    - 1934-1959, 21 folders (Box 1)
      (lacks 1950)
    - 1960-1961; include history, 1906-1961 (Box 1)
    - 1962-1966 (Box 1)
      (never received)
    - 1967-1971, 4 folders (Box 1)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1)
    - 1972-1981, 5 folders (Box 1)
- Annual and other reports
  - 1911-1923, 8 folders (Box 2)
  - 1933-1946, 13 folders (Box 2)
  - 1959-1963 (Box 2)
  - Reports of the District Federation of Women's Clubs, 1926 (Box 2)
  - Reports of the State Federation of Women's Clubs conventions, 1937-1939 (Box 2)
- Miscellanea
  - 1950-1954; include reports, clippings, etc., 2 folders (Box 2)
  - 1956-1957; include reports, newsletter, etc. (Box 2)
  - 1958-1960; include reports, budgets, etc. (Box 2)
  - Undated (Box 2)
- Treasurer's record books
  - 1907-1919 (Box 2)
  - 1925-1938 (Box 2)
  - 1907 and 1919-1925 (Box 2)
  - 1938-1954 (Box 2)
- Scrapbook
  - 1906-1935 (Box 3)
  - 1935-1946 (Box 3)
  - 1942-1944 (Box 3)
  - 1939-1976 (scattered) (Box 3)
  - 1983-1989 (Box 3)
  - 1972-1983 (Box 3)
- Photographs
  - Photo album of past presidents (Box 3)